{
    "q1" : {
        "question" : "How many cubes are there in a Rubik's cube?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "22",
            "b" : "24",
            "c" : "26",
            "d" : "28"
        },
        "correct" : "c"
    },
    "q2" : {
        "question" : "Which planet in the solar system has the most satellites?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "Saturn",
            "b" : "Venus",
            "c" : "Jupiter",
            "d" : "Mars"
        },
        "correct" : "a"
    },
    "q3" : {
        "question" : "What color is the rightmost ring in the Olympic symbols?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "Blue",
            "b" : "Yellow",
            "c" : "Red",
            "d" : "Green"
        },
        "correct" : "—Å"
    },
    "q4" : {
        "question" : "What does the Hawaiian word 'wiki' mean, which gave the Internet encyclopedia Wikipedia its name?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "Simple",
            "b" : "Quick",
            "c" : "Learned",
            "d" : "Small"
        },
        "correct" : "b"
    },
    "q5" : {
        "question" : "Which country does not cross the equator?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "Kenya",
            "b" : "Panama",
            "c" : "Brazil",
            "d" : "Indonesia"
        },
        "correct" : "b"
    },
    "q6" : {
        "question" : "How many seas surround the Balkan Peninsula?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "3",
            "b" : "4",
            "c" : "5",
            "d" : "6"
        },
        "correct" : "d"
    },
    "q7" : {
        "question" : "Who was the first to win the Nobel Prize for Literature?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "Poet",
            "b" : "Playwright",
            "c" : "Novelist",
            "d" : "Essayist"
        },
        "correct" : "a"
    },
    "q8" : {
        "question" : "How many countries are part of Great Britain?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "1",
            "b" : "3",
            "c" : "4",
            "d" : "6"
        },
        "correct" : "c"
    },
    "q9" : {
        "question" : "What ingredient do popsicles and sausages have in common?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "Sugar",
            "b" : "Chocolate",
            "c" : "Milk",
            "d" : "All answers are correct"
        },
        "correct" : "d"
    },
    "q10" : {
        "question" : "Which country has the highest mountain in the British Isles?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "England",
            "b" : "Scotland",
            "c" : "Wales",
            "d" : "Sudan"
        },
        "correct" : "b"
    },
    "q11" : {
        "question" : "This is the country where the annual Eurovision Song Contest was held for the first time in 1956?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "Switzerland",
            "b" : "France",
            "c" : "Great Britain",
            "d" : "Italy"
        },
        "correct" : "a"
    },
    "q12" : {
        "question" : "How many percent of a sloth's life are spent sleeping?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "70%",
            "b" : "75%",
            "c" : "80%",
            "d" : "85%"
        },
        "correct" : "b"
    },
    "q13" : {
        "question" : "What vitamin is not in the melon?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "A",
            "b" : "C",
            "c" : "M",
            "d" : "P"
        },
        "correct" : "c"
    },
    "q14" : {
        "question" : "What metal is necessarily present in amalgam?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "mercury",
            "b" : "lead",
            "c" : "silver",
            "d" : "copper"
        },
        "correct" : "a"
    },
    "q15" : {
        "question" : "How much should you turn the dial of a clock when you are in England to know the time in India?",
        "answers" : {
            "a" : "None",
            "b" : "90",
            "c" : "180",
            "d" : "270"
        },
        "correct" : "c"
    }

}
